<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>MAGICA By Rish Agarwal</title>
    <link href="https://magica.in/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://magica.in" />
    <updated>2022-10-08T23:25:43+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Rish</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://magica.in</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Beach Outdoor Pre Wedding Engagement Shoot</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/beach-outdoor-pre-wedding-engagement-shoot/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/beach-outdoor-pre-wedding-engagement-shoot/</id>
            <category term="Learn Photography"/>

        <updated>2022-10-08T23:25:43+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/119/asdrubal-luna-60Lu4wco62w-unsplash.jpg" alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" />
                    Shooting a pre wedding or engagement shoot at a beach is always a thrilling experience. For one, it poses a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/119/asdrubal-luna-60Lu4wco62w-unsplash.jpg" alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" />
                <p>Shooting a pre wedding or engagement shoot at a beach is always a thrilling experience. For one, it poses a challenge of sand and salty water all around (which can always very easy damage your equipment) but it also offers an opportunity to use the sunlight, sand, water all the natural elements to incorporate emotions in the photographers of our couple.</p>
<p>Here are some of our tips if you're looking to get your pre wedding shoot done at an outdoor beach:</p>
<h2>Wear comfortable clothes</h2>
<p>No matter if you're shooting at a beach in Goa, Andaman, Maldives or any other part of the world, and even if the shoot starts as a serious one, it's bound to go more fun as the time goes, and you'll be running, smiling and having a lot of fun with your partner in the shoot. So it's best to be in comfortable clothes so that you're not too much concerned about them and instead, focus on getting great fun pictures!</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/thomas-yohei-PMLL435j_V8-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="533" height="800"></figure>
<h2>Use The Contrast</h2>
<p>A beach is always going to have a lot of contrasting elements all around. Even though, our style of wedding photography is very minimalistic and modern, we always use this opportunity to include the contrasting elements of things like boats parked on the shore or any other element we can find to incorporate in our pre wedding photo shoot.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/jonathan-borba-9GkapULEiTE-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<h2>Use The Sunlight To Your Advantage</h2>
<p>This tip is for both photographers and the couples. Use that beautiful sunset light to get the best ever photographs of your beloved. Everyone looks stunning when the light of the setting sun falls on their face. Why not use this opportunity to do some romantic or even dramatic poses with your loved one and let us capture that as a lifelong memory?</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/jonathan-borba-GaSmtFJUPuE-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="533" height="800"></figure>
<h2>Be A Super Model</h2>
<p>And while you're having fun and feeling all mushy, it doesn't hurt to give some <a>poses</a> like you're in a high fashion model magazine. This especially goes if you have hired the <a>best pre wedding photographer</a> you can find because he'll have the perfect experience of not only getting the best <a>intimate pre wedding</a> shots, but also shots like these.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/asdrubal-luna-60Lu4wco62w-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<h2>It's not always about the face</h2>
<p>I know, for most of the time, you'd want to have your happy face in your pre wedding photos. But sometimes (in fact, a lot of times) some of the most powerful photos we have taken do not have faces in them. And that's because your body, hands, and legs are perfectly capable of communicating emotions through the photos. And sometimes more than you face ever can. So don't be afraid of getting shots like these:</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/joanna-nix-walkup-vgkjJlEj-VQ-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/thomas-yohei-mqRxVOC7GXo-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="533" height="800"></figure>
<h2>Be overly in love</h2>
<p>This is your pre wedding shoot and this is probably the best time to show the immense love you have to your partner. Be romantic. Do some dramatic poses. Kiss each other. Hold each other. Remember, these few hours are going to give you the photos you're going to cherish for a lifetime.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/jonathan-borba-Id4Hvej_w7k-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="533" height="800"></figure>
<h2>Shoot till the sun sets</h2>
<p>The sun is very dramatic at two times of the day: sunrise and sunset. And most probably, you'll be facing the sunset if you're doing your pre wedding shoot at an outdoor beach. Use the opportunity to the fullest and create dramatic silhouette photos while the sun is setting with your partner.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/10/jonathan-borba-VX2nrLhq4h4-unsplash.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Pre Wedding Photographer India Outdoor Beach Shoot" width="533" height="800"></figure>
<p>If you're looking to get your pre wedding shoot done at an outdoor beach location, be sure to contact us.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://magica.in/contact/" class="btn">Contact Us</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/indian-wedding-photographer-in-new-jersey-new-york-bay-area/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/indian-wedding-photographer-in-new-jersey-new-york-bay-area/</id>
            <category term="Learn Photography"/>

        <updated>2022-10-07T20:21:39+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/118/TriciaHemant_Blog_RishPhotography_036.webp" alt="" />
                    The person who captures the memories of your big day is just as important as what you wear, who you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/118/TriciaHemant_Blog_RishPhotography_036.webp" alt="" />
                <figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/PT_Day3_255.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>The person who captures the memories of your big day is just as important as what you wear, who you call to give your toast, and where you say your vows. The right <a href="https://magica.in/best-indian-wedding-photographer-in-usa/">Indian wedding photographer in USA</a> will capture those special moments in detail—and help share them with everyone else. A bad one, on the other hand, can make or break your special day. Luckily, finding a great Indian wedding photographer in New Jersey is more difficult than it seems! </p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2018/05/Puneet_Rahul_Blog_127.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>Whether you’re planning your dream wedding at a nearby venue or opting for an outside ceremony that takes place under the night sky, there are many ways to find the perfect New Jersey Indian wedding photographer for you. Here’s everything you need to know about finding the best <a href="https://magica.in">Indian wedding photographer in New Jersey</a> and New York.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/16.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<h2><strong>What to Look for in an Indian Wedding Photographer in NJ, NYC, Bay Area, Chicago &amp; California</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Experience</strong></h3>
<p>A lot of experience. Shooting <a href="https://magica.in/tags/weddings/">Indian weddings</a> is nothing less than shooting a movie. There are so many characters, so many stories, so much chaos going around and still the wedding photographer need to focus on the right things and get the emotions of the bride, groom, and their families captured in their wedding photographs. The best Indian wedding photographers have been doing this for years and know exactly how to handle each situation, how to get the best out of every person in the wedding party, and how to make sure the bride and groom are always comfortable. This is one of the main reasons why you will see so many photographers performing Indian weddings. They know how to do this, they do it well, and they are dedicated to their craft. Indian wedding photographers are some of the best at what they do, they are passionate about it, they are invested in their craft, and they know how to make a great result happen.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/NK_Day2_319.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<h3><strong>Professionalism</strong></h3>
<p>If you’re looking for a wedding photographer who is friendly, easygoing, and fun to work with, you will love our Indian wedding photographers. Yes, experience is absolutely essential, but only experience can never work without top-notch professionalism. A professional Indian wedding photographer would know how to handle all the unpredictability and stress that comes with Indian weddings. No matter, if you're getting married in New Jersey, New York, Chicago or California, your Indian wedding will come with its own set of surprises. And a professional wedding photographer will come prepared with everything. And if you want someone who will be on time, professional, and makes sure every detail is just right then you want one of our professional Indian Wedding Photographers. They’ll provide you with an amazing experience from start to finish!</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/AnshNitika_Blog_RishPhotography_083.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<h3><strong>Quality of Work</strong></h3>
<p>It’s really hard to describe your style in photography when you don’t have any samples of your work yet. To help give potential clients an idea of what they can expect from our team, we offer different packages that include a variety of prints, albums, digital images or even video services all at different price points so that everyone can find something that works for them. We also offer custom Indian wedding photography packages, so if there are specific things that are important to you such as more than one photographer or engagement session, please let us know, so we can talk about what your needs are!</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2019/05/AR_Wedding_Blog_123.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<h3><strong>Value</strong></h3>
<p>Everything in the world has a price and a value. Something really expensive can be utterly useless to you, and something very trivial can hold infinite value in your heart. Imagine that old photo of your mother when you were young. You can never put a price on that photo, but it'll always hold immense value in your heart. Similarly, your wedding photos will always be valuable to you. The wedding is a once in a lifetime event, so we always suggest our brides look for value, regardless of the price. Because money is something you can always get again. But time, you cannot.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/Nandita_Day1_Rish_91-copy.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>Finding an Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York, Bay Area, Chicago or California can be hard since most of the assignments there require them to shoot church or American weddings which are opposites to <a href="https://magica.in/indian-wedding-videographer-wedding-films/">Indian Weddings</a>. However, with our award-winning team of Magica, with over a decade of Indian wedding photography and videography, you can be rest assured that you'll be getting amazing wedding photos.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/TriciaHemant_Blog_RishPhotography_036.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in New Jersey, New York Bay Area" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<h3><strong>Final Words</strong></h3>
<p>Now that you’ve read our <a href="https://magica.in/best-wedding-photographer-in-india-or-top-10-magica-by-rish-agarwal/">New Jersey Indian Wedding Photography</a> blog, we would like to thank you for spending time with us. We hope that this article has given you a better understanding of what to look for in a good wedding photographer. We also hope that it has helped you understand why hiring an Indian wedding photographer is the best choice for your wedding. As an Indian wedding photographer, we couldn’t be more excited to help capture your special day and make sure every detail is remembered forever.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Best Indian Wedding Photographer in USA</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/best-indian-wedding-photographer-in-usa/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/best-indian-wedding-photographer-in-usa/</id>
            <category term="Learn Photography"/>

        <updated>2022-10-08T03:36:16+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/117/ANWedding_Blog_RishPhotography_032.webp" alt="" />
                    If you're an Indian bride, looking to make lifetime memories of your wedding and are on a quest to find&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/117/ANWedding_Blog_RishPhotography_032.webp" alt="" />
                <p>If you're an Indian bride, looking to make lifetime memories of your wedding and are on a quest to find the <strong>best <a href="https://magica.in/best-wedding-photographer-in-india-or-top-10-magica-by-rish-agarwal/">Indian wedding photographer</a> in the USA</strong>, I feel your pain and how difficult it can get.</p>
<div> </div>
<div>With so much of information floating around and how easy it is to just make an Instagram page, put some pictures and say that you're a wedding photographer make so much room for error of judgement. </div>
<div> </div>
<div><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/5.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in USA" width="702" height="468"></figure></div>
<div> </div>
<div>And on top of that, I have seen a lot of American wedding photographers cannot understand the essence of an Indian wedding and what an Indian bride wishes for in her wedding photos. </div>
<div> </div>
<div>And that's no fault of theirs.</div>
<div> </div>
<div>They just haven't been brought up in our culture, where our parents &amp; elders hold utmost importance. Where it's normal to invite everyone we know with their whole family and friends. Where time just lose its significance (we don't think in number of hours) and just how long and hectic Indian weddings can get (think 4-5 days and sometimes across multiple cities)</div>
<div> </div>
<div>After all, to be the best Indian <a href="https://magica.in/best-wedding-photographer-in-delhi-india/">wedding photographer</a> in the USA, you have to understand the following fundamentals of how to photograph and Indian wedding:</div>
<h2><strong>Too Many Events</strong></h2>
<div>There are just so many events across cultures in an Indian wedding. From baraat to pheras. From jaimala to joota chhupai, there are so many events that are so important to be captured in an Indian wedding that an entire encyclopedia might fell short if one has to start understanding everything. Unless someone is born and brought up in the <a href="https://magica.in/how-to-plan-an-indian-wedding-a-step-by-step-guide-for-2022-2023/">Indian culture</a>, it's very hard for them to comprehend the value of each and every ritual and the broader reason behind them. </div>
<div> </div>
<div><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/PN_Day2_Wedding_306.jpeg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in USA" width="702" height="469"></figure></div>
<h2><strong>Everyone is important</strong></h2>
<div>In no other culture in the world do we have so many guests, where everyone is important. That distant aunt, whom you didn't see after your 5th grade, has to be in the photos. That small kid you never knew existed until now has to be photographed with his family. And naturally, photographers who have had the experience of only photographing American weddings, where with the bride and groom, there are a only handful of people in the family that are there, it's really hard to understand the logic behind this. Maybe there's no logic really, but that's how Indian weddings are :)</div>
<div> </div>
<div><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2019/05/Before_After_002.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in USA" width="702" height="470"></figure></div>
<h2><strong>Nothing is on time</strong></h2>
<div>It is said that there's a world time zone and there's an IST, a.k.a. Indian Standard Time, but actually it means is Indians are Seldom on Time 🤣</div>
<div>And anyone who has ever attended an Indian wedding would wholeheartedly agree with me. In my over a decade long career as a wedding photographer, I haven't seen a single <a href="https://magica.in/how-to-plan-an-indian-wedding-a-step-by-step-guide-for-2022-2023/">Indian wedding</a> where everything went on as it was planned and on time. Once, in a wedding which I was shooting, the baraat was 6 hours late. In another one, bride and groom planned for months for a sunset wedding, but on the wedding day, nobody was ready, and the sun set at its convenient time. What would you do in such a situation? And only an experienced Indian wedding photographer would be equipped to handle that kind of stress.</div>
<h2><strong>The lighting and colours</strong></h2>
<div>English or American weddings have primarily two colours—black for the groom and white for the bride. Indian weddings on the other hand start at a minimum of 2 million colours. Just look at this photo below and try to count the number of colours.</div>
<div><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2019/05/AR_Engagement_Blog_095.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in USA" width="702" height="468"></figure></div>
<div> </div>
<div>The thing with colour is, it really depends on what light is falling on it, that what colour you'd see. So if you, as a bride, have spent months of your time and thousands of your dollars in selecting that perfect colour attire for your wedding, but the colours come out to be all off because the Indian wedding photographer couldn't handle things in tough lighting conditions, how would you feel?</div>
<h1>So here's my recommendation on selecting the best Indian wedding photographer in the USA:</h1>
<h2><strong>Get someone who gets Indian weddings:</strong></h2>
<div>This goes without saying. Get someone who specifically has the experience of shooting Indian weddings. AT LEAST 5-6 years of experience. The more, the better. Because that photographer would know how to handle all the stress and unpredictability that comes with an Indian wedding and still deliver amazing wedding photos.</div>
<div> </div>
<div><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2018/05/Puneet_Rahul_Blog_127.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in USA" width="702" height="468"></figure></div>
<h2><strong>Hire the Indian wedding photographer in the USA who has a full portfolio to show</strong></h2>
<div>Not some selected photos. Not an Instagram gallery. You really should see a <a href="https://magica.in/tags/weddings/">complete wedding coverage portfolio </a>of a single (and preferably more) Indian weddings. Why? Because that'll show how <i>consistently</i> he/she can shoot great photos.</div>
<h2><strong>Have an online / in person meeting before hiring your wedding photographer</strong></h2>
<div>This one is crucial. Despite someone having checked all the boxes above, it's possible that when you actually meet that person or team, you really don't get along with the vibe. You'd not be able to put a finger on the why you feel so, but it'll just be there. And you're going to trust that person or the wedding company for the most important day of your life. And conversely, they're also going to spend months of their life in post-processing and editing of your wedding pictures. So it's really crucial that you both like each other to be able to work effectively.</div>
<div> </div>
<div><figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/Neha_Aditya_01.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Indian Wedding Photographer in USA" width="702" height="468"></figure></div>
<div> </div>
<div>Those are the points I could think of on top of my mind right now. Did I miss anything? Do let me know on <a href="https://instagram.com/rish404">Instagram</a>.</div>
<div> </div>
<div>Here are some Indian wedding videography done by our award-winning team at Magica:</div>
<div>
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eeJ0r3S-4fQ?feature=youtu" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></figure>
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fFUla8Ebisk?feature=youtu" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></figure>
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7m4EOrBtehk?feature=youtu" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></figure>
</div>
<div> </div>
<div>Meanwhile, if you're looking for an Indian wedding photographer in the USA ideally but not limited to California, Texas, New Jersey, New York, Illinois, Florida or Washington DC area, be sure to contact us</div>
<div> </div>
<div class="align-center"><a href="https://magica.in/contact/" class="btn">Contact Us</a></div>
<div> </div>
<div> </div>
<div><strong> </strong></div>
<div> </div>
<div> </div>
<div><br>
<div> </div>
<div> </div>
<div><br>
<div> </div>
<div><br>
<div> </div>
<div> </div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Best Canon Lenses For Wedding Photography</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/the-best-canon-lenses-for-wedding-photography/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/the-best-canon-lenses-for-wedding-photography/</id>
            <category term="Learn Photography"/>

        <updated>2022-10-05T01:48:04+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/116/Neha_Aditya_01.jpg" alt="" />
                    Whether you're photographing an intimate elopement, a micro wedding, a quirky alternative wedding or a traditional big wedding reception, the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/116/Neha_Aditya_01.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="column small left"><span style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Whether you're photographing an intimate elopement, a micro wedding, a quirky alternative wedding or a traditional big wedding reception, the right kit is key. So which are the best Canon lenses for wedding photography? What are the essential features to look for in a Canon wedding lens? And which lenses will be both reliable and fast to focus, enabling you to deliver results time and time again?</span></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="#Canon RF 15-35">Best wide-angle lens</a></li>
<li><a href="#Canon RF 85mm">Best lens for details</a></li>
<li><a href="#Canon RF 40mm">Best lens for isolating the subject</a></li>
<li><a href="#Canon RF 28-70">Best zoom lens</a></li>
<li><a href="#Canon RF 70-200mm">Best lens for outdoor portraits</a></li>
<li><a href="#bonus">Bonus : My favourite lens</a></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="Canon RF 15-35">1. Best wide-angle lens for immersive portraits: Canon RF 15-35mm F2.8L IS USM</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><a href="https://amzn.to/3V1qwtC"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://i.postimg.cc/Zqbz13gB/gallery-canon-rf-15-35mm-f2.webp" data-is-external-image="true"  width="316" height="316"></figure></a></p>
<p>First of all, let's understand what immersive portraits actually mean. It's a well known fact in the photography and cinema world that you keep your audience where you put your camera (or the lens) at. Which means, when the director or the DoP decides to pan into a shot in film, you feel getting closer to the mind of the character. If the camera is far apart, you feel disconnected and if it's too close, you feel uncomfortable.</p>
<p>Similarly, in wedding photography, we're always working with human beings. And for the people who see those photos afterwards, it's very important to give them a feeling of immersion like they were actually present there at the wedding, celebrating with their loved ones. This has a great emotional impact and the primary reason why sometimes some of our clients have tears in their eyes when seeing their wedding photos for the first time.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2019/05/AR_Wedding_Blog_001.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Canon Lenses For Wedding Photography By Indian Wedding Photographer Rish Agarwal" width="702" height="469"></figure>
<p>Canon's RF 15-35mm lets you do just that. With a flexible aperture, this goes from 35mm to all the way to 15mm. So no matter the number of people in front of you, you can always adjust the focal length to include them all and capture all the drama in a single frame and give the viewer a sense of immersion.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://amzn.to/3V1qwtC" class="btn">Buy Now (Amazon IN)</a></p>
<h2 id="Canon RF 85mm">2. Best lens for capturing details: Canon RF 85mm F1.2L USM</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--right"><a href="https://amzn.to/3CzApHW"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://i.postimg.cc/6qLDjp0L/rf-85mm-f1.webp" data-is-external-image="true"  width="351" height="351"></figure></a></p>
<p>The devil is in the details. And details are the most overlooked while the most essential thing, not only in photography, but in everything else you do in your life. But especially in wedding photography, the importance of details cannot be overstated. After all, the most important things like the wedding ring, all need detailed shots.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="http://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/TriciaHemant_Blog_RishPhotography_020.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Canon Lenses For Wedding Photography By Indian Wedding Photographer Rish Agarwal" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>However, details are not only limited to just objects. Detail can be even human emotions. That tear that is just about to roll off the cheek of bride's mother, capture that detail. That twinkle in the eye when the groom sees his bride for the first time, capture that. That tightness of the hug, the father gives her daughter at the wedding, capture that. And to capture all of this, the best lens, in my opinion, would be Canon's RF 85mm F1.2L USM. Since these details happen for split seconds, you need a very fast lens. The 85mm with F1.2 is the fastest lens in that series which can lock tact sharp focus even in low light situations given the wide aperture it has.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://amzn.to/3CzApHW" class="btn">Buy Now (Amazon IN)</a></p>
<h2 id="Canon RF 40mm">3. Best lens for isolating the subject: Canon RF 50mm F1.2L USM</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://i.postimg.cc/wxX8Twpy/rf50mm-f-1.webp" data-is-external-image="true"  width="351" height="351"></figure>
<p>There's a very popular term in photography, which I'm sure most of you have heard before. And it's called Bokeh. It's the Japanese word from blur. Specifically, background blur. And what background blur essentially does it to isolate your subject. The subject then stands alone regardless of how busy or distracting the background is and you still can get a great photo. Almost all portraits depend on this background blur or bokeh effect. And Canon's RF 50mm f1.2L USM lens helps you achieve just that very easily.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/5.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Canon Lenses For Wedding Photography By Indian Wedding Photographer Rish Agarwal" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>Have a subject with a very distracting or busy background but still want to make an epic portrait? Just shoot 50mm wide open and you're golden.</p>
<p>50mm is also a very special focal length because it's closer to what our normal eyes see the world in. So, when we shoot portraits in 50mm focal length, it doesn't deform or exaggerate any facial or body features. You get what you see, just in a much more beautiful and artistic way!</p>
<h2 id="Canon RF 28-70">4. Best zoom lens for wedding photography: Canon RF 28-70mm F2L USM</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--right"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://i.postimg.cc/hvqk1d9t/rf28-70mm-f-2l-usm-side-1x1-2127c2e2d818432bad9c83bec854360a.webp" data-is-external-image="true"  width="351" height="351"></figure>
<p>Zoom is a great superpower to have. Imagine you never have to move an inch and still be able to capture anything in the line of sight. Well, a zoom lens gives you that power. But with great power comes great responsibility. And you have to really know where to use what level of zoom. Keeping that judgement aside, Canon RF 28.70 f2L USM is a great lens to have with a very wide range of zoom.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2018/05/Puneet_Rahul_Blog_127.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Canon Lenses For Wedding Photography By Indian Wedding Photographer Rish Agarwal" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>28mm is practically a very wide focal length and 70mm is a very long focal length. There's no other lens in this price range that gives you this much flexibility.</p>
<p>However, the thing with zoom lenses are they tend to be a little bit heavier, more complex and little bit slower. What I mean by slower is, the maximum aperture in this lens is f2 which is quite a bit slower than other f1.2 lenses we discussed earlier.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, if this is a tradeoff you're willing to take, this lens is very versatile.</p>
<h2 id="Canon RF 70-200mm">5. Best long lens for outdoor portraits: Canon RF 70-200mm F2.8L IS USM</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><a href="https://amzn.to/3Ey4xF1"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://i.postimg.cc/hGNWhwvx/pro-best-mirrorless-kit-landscapes-boxout-3-86cc10e9070d44d0a04b04075f97a71e.webp" data-is-external-image="true"  width="351" height="351"></figure></a></p>
<p>Although not as long as the average length of an Indian wedding, Canon RF 70-200mm f2.8L IS USM is one of the best long zoom lenses Canon has ever produced. If I have to choose one lens to shoot a whole wedding with, I'd definitely choose this lens. This lens is built like a tank, offers you an exponential range while being an L series lens (L series lenses are classic canons with a red ring, built like a tank &amp; top notch quality)</p>
<p>Why have I referred to this as best lens for outdoor portraits? Because 200mm is such a long focal length, the photographer needs to stand very far away from the subject in order to photograph it. Otherwise the lens just won't focus. But once you get a taste of that 200mm quality, bokeh &amp; speed, it's very hard to go back.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/04/KJ_TajShoot_Mehtab_Morning_059.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Canon Lenses For Wedding Photography By Indian Wedding Photographer Rish Agarwal" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>Since this lens comes at the maximum aperture of f.28 it requires great lighting to work at its full potential. And what better light source than our good old sun? This is why I prefer this lens while working in outdoor conditions with an open sky and ample of light.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://amzn.to/3Ey4xF1" class="btn">Buy Now (Amazon IN)</a></p>
<h2 id="bonus">6. Bonus - Canon RF 35mm f/1.8 Macro is STM Lens</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--right"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://i.postimg.cc/mZCVHr8h/rf35mm-f-1.webp" data-is-external-image="true"  width="320" height="320"></figure>
<p>This one is a bonus and let me tell you why. The 35mm is a very well kept secret of all great documentary photographers. Why is that you ask? That's because 35mm is the exact focal length of our eyes. Which makes the photos produced by this lens really familiar. Because that's how we see the world with our own eyes!</p>
<p>But this one has one more amazing trick right up its sleeve. This RF 35mm f/1.8 lens comes with macro ability inbuilt.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/Neha_Aditya_01.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Best Canon Lenses For Wedding Photography By Indian Wedding Photographer Rish Agarwal" width="702" height="468"></figure>
<p>Which means you not only can create great photographic compositions using its 35mm focal length, but also can get detailed close up macro shots using the macro mode. That's two very expensive to have features in a relatively inexpensive lens. And that too, at a fast aperture speed of f1.8. What more can you want?</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://amzn.to/3fAxaXn" class="btn">Buy Now (Amazon IN)</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Couple Photo Shoot At Taj Mahal</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/couple-photo-shoot-at-taj-mahal/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/couple-photo-shoot-at-taj-mahal/</id>

        <updated>2022-09-29T23:48:02+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Taj Mahal is an epitome of love. Originally built by the Emperor of Mughals - Shah Jahan in the memory&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Taj Mahal is an epitome of love. Originally built by the Emperor of Mughals - Shah Jahan in the memory of his beloved wife, Mumtaz mahal, it's one of the seven wonders of the world, situated in Agra, India. What can be more beautiful than getting your pre wedding engagement shoot done at this majestic location?</p>
<p>We offer the <a href="https://magica.in/tags/pre-wedding/">Best Pre Wedding Engagement Shoot At Taj Mahal</a> in India. We're licensed photographers to shoot there so you don't have to face any issues while getting the photo shoot there.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/04/KJ_TajShoot_Mehtab_Morning_059.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p>Here are some posts you should see:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p class="post__title"><a href="https://magica.in/how-to-plan-a-pre-wedding-shoot-at-taj-mahal/">How To Plan A Pre Wedding Shoot At Taj Mahal</a></p>
</li>
<li><a href="https://magica.in/taj-mahal-pre-wedding-engagement-shoot/">Taj Mahal Pre Wedding Engagment Shoot</a></li>
<li><a href="https://magica.in/taj-mahal-pre-wedding-rish-photography/">With Love From Taj</a></li>
</ul>
<p>If you're looking for best pre wedding engagement shoot at Taj Mahal, do contact us today!</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://form.jotform.com/222465137386056" class="btn">Contact Us</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How To Plan A Pre Wedding Shoot At Taj Mahal</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/how-to-plan-a-pre-wedding-shoot-at-taj-mahal/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/how-to-plan-a-pre-wedding-shoot-at-taj-mahal/</id>

        <updated>2022-09-23T19:37:51+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Taj Mahal is an epitome of love. Originally built by the Emperor of Mughals - Shah Jahan in the memory&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Taj Mahal is an epitome of love. Originally built by the Emperor of Mughals - Shah Jahan in the memory of his beloved wife, Mumtaz mahal, it's one of the seven wonders of the world, situated in Agra, India. What can be more beautiful than getting your pre wedding engagement shoot done at this majestic location?</p>
<p>We offer the <a href="https://magica.in">Best Pre Wedding Engagement Shoot At Taj Mahal</a> in India. We're licensed photographers to shoot there so you don't have to face any issues while getting the photo shoot there.</p>
<p class="msg--highlight msg">Here's why you should consider getting your pre wedding photo shoot done at Taj:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Iconic Location</strong> - There's literally no other location in the world that you can compare with the majestic Taj Mahal</li>
<li><strong>Easy Access</strong> - Agra is just a drive away from New Delhi, which is also one of the biggest international airports in India. You can be anywhere in the world, just land at New Delhi airport and travel to Agra by road or train and get your shoot done!</li>
<li><strong>The Ultimate Heritage: </strong>Taj Mahal is the ultimate mughal monument and it was also called as the "Jewel of Muslim Art in India". So if you fancy yourself in traditional Indian lehenga or anarkali, there can be no better background than a heritage site and that too, Taj Mahal for getting your engagement or <a href="https://magica.in/taj-mahal-pre-wedding-engagement-shoot/">pre wedding shoot </a>done.</li>
<li><strong>Beautiful Surroundings</strong> - The Taj is not only Taj. It has amazing beautiful surrounds like <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mehtab_Bagh">Mehtab Bagh</a> which is across the river Yamuna and through where, the whole Taj is visible in all its glory. Here's how it looks like in photos:</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2022/04/KJ_TajShoot_Mehtab_Morning_059.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  loading="lazy" data-is-external-image="true"></p>
<p class="msg msg--success">Some points which you should also note before you plan for the shoot:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Avoid Fridays - </strong>Taj Mahal is closed for general viewing on Friday. Although, you still can have your shoot done at Mehtab Bagh during early morning or late evening hours, you would not be able to go inside Taj and enjoy its beauty</li>
<li><strong>Sunrise vs Sunset Shoot - </strong>As a photographer, I'd always prefer sunrise over sunset because everything from surroundings to your mood is fresh &amp; we have seen much better shoot take place in mornings instead of evenings. However, evenings also have their own advantage and you can also include the <strong>boating area shoot</strong> in your plan if you're shooting in evening</li>
<li><strong>Check for weather -</strong> Whenever you're planning for your pre wedding shoot at Taj Mahal, it's always a good idea to check the weather updates for Agra. It gets really hot during summers in Agra and we'll recommend you to avoid visiting in peak summer months. Winters might be a better option to get your pre wedding shoot done.</li>
<li><strong>No changing rooms - </strong>Since Taj is a heritage site, you don't have the luxury of changing rooms in or around the area. It's always best to decide the best dresses for your shoot and commit to them. Rest is done by your enthusiasm 😄</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2015/12/NK_PreWed_79-Edit.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  loading="lazy" data-is-external-image="true"></p>
<p class="msg msg--highlight">Permissions &amp; Constraints</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>No Video Shooting Allowed - </strong>Unfortunately, there's no video shooting possible at Taj Mahal. Only Photography</li>
<li><strong>No Props - </strong>You will not be carry any fancy props inside the premises of Taj Mahal. But hey, keep it as natural as you can which is always the best opiont!</li>
<li><strong>No Drone Camera </strong>- Taj Mahal and its vicinity is protected by strict aviation laws and no one can fly a drone around there</li>
<li><strong>Style of Dresses - </strong>Our recommendation as wedding photographers is to choose plain &amp; solid colors instead of anything flashy when it comes to choosing your attires because that looks best in front of the all-white Taj Mahal</li>
<li><strong>Permission Costs - </strong>Other than the entry fee, there will be permission costs if you want to do a pre wedding shoot at Taj Mahal. For details, make sure to contact us today</li>
</ul>
<p>So, if you want to plan a magical <a href="https://magica.in/taj-mahal-pre-wedding-engagement-shoot/">pre wedding shoot at Taj Mahal </a>to be pretty much alive in your memories, well don’t look beyond as we are right here to make your dream shoot a reality. We bet your photos will turn out to be gorgeous and you will be creating memories that you will cherish forever.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://form.jotform.com/222465137386056" class="btn">Contact Us</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Best Wedding Photographer In India | Top 10 Magica By Rish Agarwal</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/best-wedding-photographer-in-india-or-top-10-magica-by-rish-agarwal/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/best-wedding-photographer-in-india-or-top-10-magica-by-rish-agarwal/</id>

        <updated>2022-10-03T02:45:23+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/105/PN_Day2_Wedding_306.jpeg" alt="" />
                    A wedding is one of the most special days of a couple’s lives. It’s an event where two people become&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/105/PN_Day2_Wedding_306.jpeg" alt="" />
                <p dir="auto" data-pm-slice="1 1 []">A wedding is one of the most special days of a couple’s lives. It’s an event where two people become one and celebrate with family and friends.</p>
<p dir="auto">Weddings are beautiful and full of love. The planning process can be stressful, but when all the details come together on your special day, it’s all worth it. That’s why we offer wedding planning services to help you with every detail from start to finish.</p>
<p dir="auto"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/5.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p dir="auto">In order to make the planning process a little easier, we offer best wedding photography services. We’ll take care of the difficult details so you can focus on what matters most: your love and commitment. Our wedding planning experts will help you plan every aspect of your ceremony, from venue and catering to flowers and entertainment.</p>
<p dir="auto"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2019/05/AR_Engagement_Blog_095.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p dir="auto">So why not make sure that every moment is captured perfectly? Hiring a professional wedding photographer ensures that you get the perfect photos that you will treasure forever. . We all know how important it is to have a professional best wedding photographer on your side, but many photographers are unaffordable for most people.</p>
<p dir="auto"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2019/05/Before_After_002.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<h3 dir="auto">How to Choose the <a href="http://magica.in">Best Wedding Photographer</a> for You</h3>
<p dir="auto">Choosing the right wedding photographer is a critical decision that can make or break your big day. It’s important to find someone who will be able to capture the moments in a way that you can treasure forever.</p>
<p dir="auto"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/Neha_Aditya_01.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p dir="auto">You may want to consider some of these factors when choosing your wedding photographer:</p>
<p dir="auto"><strong>- Budget:</strong> Wedding photographers come with different price points, so it’s important to know what you can afford before making any commitments.</p>
<p dir="auto"><strong>- Style:</strong> Do you want traditional posed photos or something more candid? You should also think about how formal or informal you want the photos to be.</p>
<p dir="auto"><strong>- Skill level: </strong>A professional photographer will likely have more experience than an amateur, so it’s worth considering if this is something that matters to you.</p>
<p dir="auto"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/PN_Day2_Wedding_306.jpeg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p dir="auto">At Magica By Rish Agarwal, we’re the Best &amp; <a href="http://magica.in">Top 10 wedding photographers</a> in India. We’re based out of New Delhi and shoot weddings all across the world</p>
<p class="align-center" dir="auto"><strong><a href="https://magica.in/contact/" class="btn">Contact Us</a></strong></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Best Wedding Photographer In Delhi, India</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/best-wedding-photographer-in-delhi-india/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/best-wedding-photographer-in-delhi-india/</id>

        <updated>2022-09-26T15:28:57+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/104/PN_Day2_Wedding_306.jpeg" alt="" />
                    We offer our services at affordable prices. You will get high quality photographs from us. We also provide freebies such&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/104/PN_Day2_Wedding_306.jpeg" alt="" />
                <h2>We offer our services at affordable prices. You will get high quality photographs from us. We also provide freebies such as albums, prints, etc.</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/5.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><span data-offset-key="ffdo1-0-0">We are one of the <a href="http://magica.in">top wedding photographers in Delhi,India</a>. We have been providing professional photography services to people who are looking for wedding photographer in Delhi, India. We have been offering our services since 2009. We have worked with various clients across different locations. We have provided them with high quality photographs. We have also offered them with freebies such as albums and prints. We have been able to capture the moments of their special day in an artistic manner. We have been able provide our services at affordable rates.</span></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" dir="auto" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2019/05/AR_Engagement_Blog_095.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p dir="auto">There are a few key things that you need to think about before you take any photos: lighting, composition, and editing.</p>
<p dir="auto">Lighting is one of the most important aspects when it comes to photography. You should always try and shoot in natural light as much as possible. This will allow you to take photos with more depth and texture than if you were using artificial light sources like flash photography.</p>
<p dir="auto"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/11/Neha_Aditya_01.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<h2>We have worked with couples from different backgrounds and religions. We understand how important it is to capture the moments of your special day.</h2>
<p><span data-offset-key="3ojrh-0-0">We offer a wide range of photography services at affordable prices. We also provide our clients with an extensive list of packages so that they can choose the right package according to their budget.</span></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2017/07/PN_Day2_Wedding_306.jpeg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<h2>Our services include:</h2>
<p><span data-offset-key="2e5f4-0-0">We offer a wide variety of photography services such as engagement photos, bridal portraits, family portraits, baby pictures, maternity sessions, senior portrait, etc.</span></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.rishabhagarwal.com/wp-content/new-uploads/2018/05/Puneet_Rahul_Blog_127.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<h2>Contact us today!</h2>
<p><span data-offset-key="1j9k8-0-0">If you are looking for wedding photographer in Delhi,India then we would love to hear from you. You can contact us by filling up the form below. We will respond to you within 24 hours.</span></p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://magica.in/contact/" class="btn">Contact Us</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Press Mentions &amp; Coverage</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/press-mentions-and-coverage/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/press-mentions-and-coverage/</id>
            <category term="Media &amp; Press Features"/>

        <updated>2022-09-14T03:16:05+05:30</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/103/2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/Qt91qBYD/2.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/4dQZqPSQ/Asiana-Wedding-pg-54.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/yYdBpFX0/Asiana-Wedding-pg-55.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/sgGzssLX/Cover-page-Asiana-Wedding.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/763YDwf7/Daily-Post.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/qvF7x1Pt/Hindustan-Times-e-Paper-Hindustan-Times-Delhi-23-Nov-2013-Page-55.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/0QR2Lb2P/HT-feature.jpg" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.postimg.cc/GhV0M6p1/HT-feature-full-image.png" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Official Microsoft Windows Theme By Rish Agarwal</title>
        <author>
            <name>Rish</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://magica.in/official-microsoft-windows-theme-by-rish-agarwal/"/>
        <id>https://magica.in/official-microsoft-windows-theme-by-rish-agarwal/</id>
            <category term="Media &amp; Press Features"/>

        <updated>2022-09-14T03:07:09+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/102/lemon.jpg" alt="" />
                    Thanks Microsoft for considering my photos in the Captured Moments theme for your Windows users across the world Link To&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://magica.in/media/posts/102/lemon.jpg" alt="" />
                <h3 class="align-center">Thanks Microsoft for considering my photos in the Captured Moments theme for your Windows users across the world</h3>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://apps.microsoft.com/store/detail/moments-captured-by-rish-agarwal/9P1B6KFXMF1H?hl=en-us&amp;gl=us" class="btn">Link To The Theme</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.64536.14510287941342286.e84b4bd5-c46b-435d-8ff4-5cfb3ba01866.b3b5b03e-5e27-43f4-ac19-48ba6826916d" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://img.utdstc.com/screen/c4d/4c1/c4d4c17ce2c40932fd9203272f0bad9ce2c66d8cde00ef42036a1b8d87c76ac6:800" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://img.utdstc.com/screen/ca6/5f9/ca65f9743dda909525b0d3cee94f7e649deaac44ca9903e67878f60c42111fa7:800" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://img.utdstc.com/screen/134/691/1346917d51122096faab76a6f85e254e430aeed6433a5372e87d5b82289cea2f:800" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://img.utdstc.com/screen/c1e/22b/c1e22b9e4967686bf4c813886e3c1373412f1350d500b0705b53b0e096593f26:800" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://img.utdstc.com/screen/4dc/8c9/4dc8c9675523dc0794b82a45cad18d46a11bc401e275397ad92efc421a9d3352:800" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://img.utdstc.com/screen/69e/ebd/69eebdfa039fc701b8257bd736f6c180f4ea59807b268844ccd8123a19cf2f48:800" data-is-external-image="true" ></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
